"Minister Kim's Dream Life"
Wait until it's done
you like this
Sprinkle some sand on top
When there are clumps, sweep them up
Then fall here
That's fine
Do you even have to clean up dog poop?
Yes
Attention all staff
Thank you all for your hard work this morning
It’s lunch time from now till 1pm
Wish you all a happy meal
It’s time to eat!
You have to run fast if you want to have lunch here.
What?
- Otherwise, I won’t even be able to drink the soup.
- OK
You can only get one box of yogurt per person!
good
Really
Goodbye
- Hello!
- Hi yo!
- Oops!
- Hey
Good shot!
You really haven't done anything and are leaving.
I have nothing to do
Obviously there is
That doesn't count as work
Just running errands
We're taking advantage of the fact that you didn't do anything.
don't think like that
The headquarters will press harder
I heard they are closing the factory
Why are you so surprised? We heard the news too
The pressure from the headquarters will increase.
The days to come will be more difficult
I haven't accomplished anything
You did it
The earth will be destroyed tomorrow
Can it be the same as the destruction a year later?
How precious was that year?
Whether it's hiding underground or escaping to another planet
We all have time to plan
You can also spend precious time with your family
Isn't it?
After all, thanks to you
Only factory employees can be safe and sound
You can take credit
If you want to say that...
At least throw me a surprise farewell party
- What?
- Or at least
Send a message card written by everyone
Say thank you to me
But there wasn't even anyone to see him off.
They all just care about playing football
Isn't it enough for me to come?
Not enough. I like the formation to be bigger.
I'm so sorry
If I had known earlier
Even if we prepare a group gymnastics performance, that would be great
Forget it
I even showed my hand
I made some bomb wine for you.
Ah, right
I've never forgotten that glass of wine
It tastes really good
Then continue to miss me
After all, you’ll never be able to drink again.
I'm leaving
Can you give me a business card?
You really know how to choose your time.
Just give me one
ACT sells a set of...
I'm Kim Nak-soo
I am Li Zhuying, the work team leader of the production team.
(ACT Sales Group Manager Kim Nak-soo)
(ACT Production Team Lee Joo-young)
Team Leader Jin, thank you for your hard work!
Yeah
Good work thank you
Thank you for your hard work
thank you
- thank you
(ACT staff dormitory)
Episode 8: All or Nothing
(Minister Kim Nak-soo has left the group chat)
Minister Kim quits the group...
- Minister Dou, we had lunch...
- You are back
- How was your lunch?
- Let's sleep a little longer.
- It's not lunch break yet
- No, I was thinking of ideas.
First proposed in public places
People who set up and promote wireless zones
It's Kim Nak-soo, do you know?
Really? He's such a legend
He is a respectable person
It's a shame that this happened
What happened?
Teacher Song doesn’t know either?
Senior resigned today
- What?
- No wonder he quit the group
If I had told you earlier
We can also prepare a farewell party
It's a pity that we didn't even get a chance to say goodbye
Those who want to go will always go, and those who want to stay will always stay.
Minister, there's something wrong in the conference room.
- We went to conference room A instead.
- Okay, let's go.
Are you going somewhere?
- Do we have a meeting in the afternoon?
- No
I don’t think it’s necessary for a group to participate
So I didn’t tell you
There is something you need to know
I'll let Agent Li convey it to me.
from now on
- let's go
Yes Minister
What does this mean? Section Chief
This obviously means
We are Kim Nak Soo’s people after all
Breakfast is ready!
Good
Soo Gyeom, come and eat
So delicious
What's wrong with you?
It’s really delicious. Soo-gyeom, try it now.
Husband, you said before
When will the results of your physical examination come out?
Next week
I'll make an appointment for a consultation. I'll go with you.
I have to hear what the doctor says with my own ears
It's not necessary. I'm sure it will be fine.
listen to me
You can't care less about your body
Then you will have to spend a lot of money on medical expenses
Come and eat some of this too
Also, insurance should be reduced.
The little you can save on fixed expenses is worth it
Soo Gyeom just in case
You should also ask about student loans.
Good
What kind of loan? I will take care of the tuition fees.
Oops
Husband, I have to get ready.
- You haven't even finished your meal yet.
- Oh my god
Husband, when we go camping later
Wear this suit?
Shave your beard too
- This looks neater
- OK
dad
Huh?
That...
Is it what we were talking about before?
Give me some more time. I'm already working on it.
No, I want to tell you
Liar caught
- Really?
- Right
You don't have to worry anymore
Dad, I'm leaving first
Don't worry, let's go together
I'm going to be late
Oops
- Husband, what are you doing? I'm going to be late.
- OK
Goodbye Soo Kyum
This is my fourth interview
A kid much younger than me said
"Miss Park Ha-jin, why should I hire you?"
It really destroyed my self-confidence.
So I told you before
Don’t waste your time trying to get your real estate agent license
Why do you want to listen to that?
Do you think I want to listen?
It’s not all about supporting the family
Alas, forget it
Hey, don't be late when you go to the campground later.
Ha Young said it was hard to get the reservation.
Do I have to go?
Of course you have to go
This is a party I specially arranged for you
Let's go and listen to what Sang-cheol has to say, okay?
I don't barbecue
Got it, I'll have a barbecue
Is it here?
- Come on
- See you later
- OK
(Dohan Real Estate)
Hello
(Friendly advice and honest service)
- Please sit down
- OK
Oops
(Yansi University)
(Pick up meals on demand to avoid waste)
- Hello
- hello
Hello
- Hi
- Soo Gyom, you’re here
- Hello
- Go get ready.
- OK
Auntie, I put it here
Good
Su Qian, hurry up and pack up and go back.
Good bye
Goodbye
(Export)
Is this the career you said you wanted to do together?
I have to go in
Didn't we prove that we are capable?
I know you don't want to rely on your dad...
My dad said he would give me the money, but I said he wouldn’t want it.
Why?
No why
Since he said he would give you money, just accept it.
You can give it back to him later
What's wrong with this?
Hello
What did my dad do wrong?
What?
Why does my dad have to invest in us?
you can...
You can ask your parents for help.
When did I ask your dad to invest in us?
Was it me who suggested borrowing money from your father?
That's not true. But what's going on with your attitude?
Who do you think got me into this mess?
Blame me again?
Is it all because I introduced you to Li Zhenghuan?
ok
Give me your account
I'll help you pay back your 30 million. Give me your account number.
Here, take this money first
I'll call you the rest later
- Hannah
- I thought about it
I'm going back to the United States
We should really put everything
Stay in the beautiful memories of middle school
Sorry Soo Gyom
I messed everything up
I'll tell my parents as soon as I get back
Send you the money
It won't be long. Take care.
I thought we were going to grill our own meat
No, they will help with everything.
thank you
It’s not quite what we thought of camping.
- Right
- I really should have brought Soo-gyeom with me.
- Have fun
- thank you
Brother-in-law, you have worked hard these years
Don't do this
I wish you good health in the second act of your life
Congratulations, brother-in-law
- I wish you a prosperous career
- thank you
But why did you resign?
Nothing interesting anymore
Want to try a new way of living
Many companies have already invited him to work
Of course
After all, my brother-in-law has worked in a large company for 25 years.
I recently hired a sales director
It took a lot of effort
After all, I always take you as the standard in my heart
Everyone seems to think it's funny
Really?
If you want to open a company, you have to recruit people.
What will the brother-in-law do next?
Any plans?
The severance pay shouldn't be much, I guess.
more than you think
Oops, you are really worrying so much.
My brother-in-law must have a plan, right?
- Right
- So
I want to know what the plan is? What is it?
Where is the restroom?
I'll take you there
- This way
- Eat it
I'll be right back
-Brother-in-law, go this way
- OK thank you
I heard from your sister that you wanted to ask me to work before?
Yes
The timing didn't seem right at the time.
Are you interested now?
Didn’t you say you’ve already hired someone?
The more people doing sales, the better.
Really?
But if you decide to join us
You may have to work under a senior for a while first
What then?
In that case, I might not be able to give it.
The treatment I originally wanted to give you
Why, are you going to give me 2 million won?
Oh my God, brother-in-law, of course not
What's wrong? 2 million is okay, right?
I have to give you at least 2.2 million or 2.3 million won
Brother-in-law, I sincerely want to invite you to our company
wait a moment
Hello Director Yan
Well, it's convenient for me to talk
see you later
Yes I saw it
What else do investors want?
Investor Relations What else?
This bastard...
hey
- I don't know...
- Wait, let me talk first.
I'm just saying this just in case
There is no shortage of people in his company now.
I don't want you to get your hopes up too high
The invitation was a few months ago
My brother-in-law said he wasn't interested at the time.
There's no chance now
Don't tell me you asked me out today
Just for this
No, of course not
Of course not, right?
I was almost disappointed
The aloof Park Ha-jin
She would definitely not ask me to help her husband find a job.
How is it possible
- Hello!
- I remembered
I heard that the director’s subordinates
It seems true
We still need to recruit one more person.
It's my first time now
experienced a
The feeling of being able to hold you tight
- Really?
- Yeah
The sister who nags her all the time like her mother
Now because of my husband’s work
tremble before me
hey
Isn’t Sang Cheol back yet?
He came out first
Brother-in-law! Be nice to my sister
I've always been nice to her
My sister really loves you
- OK
- Okay, just do it.
Okay, I understand. Thank you for your hard work.
Who were you calling just now?
Director Yan
Is he someone hired to take the brother-in-law's place?
Yes
So is there a place for him now?
Ouch, I really hope my brother-in-law can join us.
Brother-in-law, please consider my proposal.
What a good wife
What?
nothing
Our happy Ha Young
Please consider it carefully
I promise not to nag you like mom again
I will treat you well, okay?
Please
good
- Stop drinking.
- It's okay
are you okay?
What about you? Are you okay?
I'm fine. What can happen to me?
Then I'm fine
(Representative of Sol Energy Technology, Cho Yunhyung)
Has your company's sales manager resigned?
I'll keep in touch bye
Nothing happens
Didn't you say before that the head of the department resigned?
Damn it’s so hard
(Representative of Sol Energy Technology, Cho Yunhyung)
You complained about them back then
Said they were terrible at their jobs
I also like drinking with you the most
When shall we meet?
Do you want me to come over?
Can you teach me point-of-sales tips?
Okay, you came just in time
I want to open a new branch
If someone like Minister Kim were in charge
I feel more at ease
Branch? Where is it?
(Representing Jinlun Association)
In Jamsil
I plan to make one
One-stop center from experience to sales
This is definitely the retail trend today
You have such a good eye
If you continue to mix in plain words and honorifics like this,
Let's stop talking
You go on.
The basic salary is two per month, and the rest is based on commission.
Two?
Not 20 million
(Representative Jang Min-kyu)
The most I can give is 2 million
2.2 million won
before tax
- We can't afford to hire people right now.
- Got it
You were born in 1972
- Which university did you attend in 1991?
- Right
Got it
Our representative was born in 1976
Sales! It’s so important
So I personally run the business of our company.
Wow, can you work overtime on weekends?
- Right
- Awesome!
In that case...
2 million
Aren’t sales base salaries very low?
It's all based on commission
But this is too low!
I was the director of a large company last week
I can't work with such a small salary.
Even the monthly salary of a convenience store delivery driver
Already 5 million
Then go do that
I don't have a truck license
Yes, that's true
Then just continue to live off your retirement pay.
please
How do you live?
What do you mean?
What do you do every day?
after i get up in the morning
Go exercise first, then go home and take a shower
Read the newspaper and have dinner with my wife
cut
Eat out occasionally
Then on the way home, I stopped by to take a look at my building.
Sometimes I go hiking
That's pretty much it
That’s great. A person with a monthly income of 30 million
The life we lead is indeed different
Didn’t I tell you? It’s 32 million now
I still have shares in the cafe
(32 million won per month)
I'm so envious of you, Mr. Charterer
Don't do it
What not to do?
no matter what
Never do that thing you are thinking about right now.
stop immediately
Never touch your severance pay
Leave it alone
If a person insists on doing something that is not suitable for him
It will break down the body
Find a job now
You were born to work
(NTC credit card
1,687,150 won has been deducted successfully)
Alas, the credit card was charged again
You can't spend money like you did when you were at work.
You have to save some flowers
Hello, I treat you today
So listen to me talk a few more words
Canned yellow peaches, smoked chicken legs
And spicy beef jerky, right?
Thank you, charterer
Some more dried fish
Ouch, you have a great appetite
thank you take care
(Recruiting delivery driver with a monthly salary of 5 million won)
Convenience store delivery driver makes $5 million
Courier earns 3.5 million
Drivers earn about 4 million
The pension is about 6 million
Golf instructor makes $7 million
6 million, 7 million, 6...
Hello, gentlemen.
We would like to introduce to you two
A very nice commercial building
(The monthly salary will be cut off and the monthly rent will not be)
If you invest now
You can collect six to seven million won in monthly rent in the future
Hey, I'm going home. Let's chat another time.
- Sorry
- Hey Luo Su!
Where are you going?
Hello!
(The monthly salary will be cut off and the monthly rent will not be)
Our store here is still selling it
But you have to come here as soon as possible
Not much left now
Please get a leaflet
- thank you
Please get a fan
You can go in and have a consultation.
Did you know?
The monthly salary will be cut off...
- No monthly rent!
- Please go in and have a look.
- thank you
- Please come in
Yes, you can go in directly
(Model room shop is for sale)
- Please come and take a look
- You can just take a look at it
Hello, take a fan
I'm also looking forward to working with you
Hello, welcome to AP Royal. Do you have an appointment?
No, I just came over to take a look
Welcome boss
- Have you called to make an appointment?
- No
Sorry
Our consultation appointments are fully booked today
How long until the next appointment?
About 15 minutes?
Boss, I'm afraid I only have about 15 minutes
- Do you think it will work?
- OK
Please come here
(AP Royal Wangzhen Shopping Center Sales Office)
Beverages include coffee, green tea, Shuanghe soup, and coix tea
What would you like to drink?
Just a cup of hot coffee
Have a cup of hot coffee
Good
Why did you want to come to us today?
You really don’t remember me?
You gave me a flyer at a convenience store before
Yes, yes, I remembered
What a fate
Have you sold it?
These seem to be sold out
You're late, boss.
Now there is only one house left that I can show you.
That set is really good
But the price is a bit high. I’m embarrassed to recommend it.
Listen to it. You said you are pressed for time.
Okay, let me give you a brief introduction.
(Wangzhen Shopping Center)
First of all, the location of this shop is very good
No need to talk about this part
I’ve seen the news about the extension of Line 5
Then I will add something
Yesterday I walked from the subway entrance to the shop in person
We have always advertised that it is a five-minute walk
Guess what? It’s just a three-minute walk.
People who sell houses always say it’s “very close” to the subway station.
It's really only a three-minute walk away.
That doesn't make any sense. It only works if there is a large flow of people.
There is huge potential for business development here
Look at this
The headquarters of a large IT company is to be built nearby
Project has been approved
Almost all the 50,000 residents in the surrounding communities have moved in.
There are schools nearby
so i think
Traffic flow and crowd quality here
Almost comparable to Gangnam Station
Gangnam Station? That’s too exaggerated.
- Boss, I am a professional
- Right
I have been in business for so many years
This location is definitely one of the best.
But compared to Gangnam Station...
thank you
- your coffee
- thank you
It turns out it’s a good school district.
So which stores are there now?
Please look at the first floor
A restaurant chain and a large drugstore have signed up
The second to fifth floors are clinics
Dentistry, Psychiatry, Paediatrics, Dermatology
Interior decoration will begin soon
The basement is still empty
There is a well-known Internet celebrity who wants to be on the underground floor
Open a large indoor golf club
Come and take a look at the overall layout
Still missing a business format
What do you think?
Well...
Boss, let me give you a tip.
- OK
- here
(chain restaurant)
You come out from the restaurant after eating...
Oh, coffee. There's no cafe.
You react so quickly
Now we are in harmony
Five chain coffee brands are in talks
They all think this position is inevitable
Which ones are they?
The competition is too fierce for me to disclose.
Is this one of them?
As long as you have an idea
The most promising one right now is this one
They never miss prime locations
Their market analysis is impeccable
Big companies are always very harsh.
(Mocha bean coffee)
Could you please...
I actually
Worked at ACT for almost 25 years
I just resigned
No wonder
You have the aura of a big company executive at first glance
I got a little fed up and resigned.
So where is this shop?
Look here, right around the corner
This is the only one left
I knew it was there
I noticed that location from the beginning
This kind of corner shop can attract customers from both sides.
Oops
How come you are so knowledgeable?
Oh, it's true
The monthly rent for a shop in this location is about RMB 6...
seven...
Almost nine million
That's it
you must already know
No, I thought it was about eight million
That's it. Nine million...
This row is indeed eight million
So this one is at least nine million
- That's it
- Right
Including VAT, it’s almost 9.9 million
You can just rent it for 10 million a month.
Monthly rent of 10 million?
Rent 10 million per month
10 million monthly rent 10 million
(10 million won per month)
Okay, the monthly rent is 10 million
What's the total price?
- 1.6 billion won
- What?
1.6 billion
Oops, too expensive
- boss
- Huh?
The most important thing about a shop is whether it can be rented out
And it’s hard to keep this position empty.
A very reliable investment.
I know that
But the fixed price is 1.6 billion with no discount?
please
As I said just now, you are really late
All our previous promotions have ended
So it’s really hard to get a discount. I’m sorry.
It's a pity, but there's nothing we can do about it
- I'll just...
- boss
Are you interested?
I have to see if you have any intention...
- Boss!
- You grab my hand and fuck it...
Please sit down for a while
Didn't you say you don't have time?
- Please sit down for a moment
- Oops
Oh, it's true
You are really a good bargainer.
Okay then I...
I'll ask the headmaster
Have anything to ask?
It's definitely not your turn to make the decision, right?
nothing
He has very good ears
This electric tension
This desperate feeling
Nak Soo who earns tens of millions per month!
Come to work next Monday!
Really?
You used to be the queen of credit card sales.
How could we not hire you?
Show your strength
OK, of course
I will do my best
Ouch
There's no need to cry
I just suddenly thought of my husband
Where is he?
Oops Kim Nak Soo
Answer the phone quickly! Why don't you answer the phone?
(He Zhen)
wait a moment
This is the pre-sale price a year ago
I told the head of department that you used to be an executive of ACT
He said: "Hey, then we are no match for him."
So he will give you the best price directly
I was shocked when I heard it
So 1.1 billion won? This can buy a good apartment.
Spend all this money on shops?
Chief
- Ah, is it time?
- Are you leaving?
give me five more minutes
Just five minutes
five minutes
Boss, let’s think about it from another angle?
- What do you think?
- Here...
- Yeah
- ...no resale restrictions
You can sell it immediately after you buy it
So you spend 1.1 billion won to buy it
Turn around and add an extra 400 million to sell on the market
Will take action immediately
You can make 400 million just by sitting down
Got it. Why are you so excited? Calm down.
So...
- Let’s make it 100 million cheaper.
- What?
- One billion won
- No way
Just one billion
There are a lot of customers willing to buy it at the original price of 1.6 billion.
It's more cost-effective for us to sell to them
Wait
Then just sell it to them directly for 1.6 billion.
Why do you want to sell it to me cheaply?
Even so, you know why I
Do you want to get such a favorable price for you?
Why?
because i believe you
I will manage this shop carefully
Oops
How do you know I was in management before?
You are so awesome
Boss, I have dealt with many people.
You can feel it just by looking at it
“This is a man who is good at managing
He is a person who can achieve results."
OK I got it
I will manage it well
Then let’s do a deal of one billion
No, ouch
You go, I'm going to be late
Come on, you must want to
You should sell it quickly so that you can close the stall.
Labor costs, operating costs
plus those propagandists
You have to burn several million won a day
So, dealing with an old Jianghu like you
What gives me the most headache
You know everything
I'll take a look at a place like this
You can get an estimate right away
This is nothing
Okay, okay then
In that case
One billion and fifty million
What's 50 million? Just one billion
No
Just go away. I really can't pay you this price.
Why are you so extreme? We were talking...
- What's wrong?
- Wait, let me take a call.
- I hung up on all the calls that were made to me.
- It's the boss
We'll just...
- Ouch
- Are you on your way?
Good
I was just giving another client
Introduce that set of shops?
- We just finished talking
- What does "just finished chatting" mean?
No. I will be available to see you after my next appointment.
Okay, see you later
Good bye
Wait what?
Hey, we're not done talking yet. I haven't decided yet.
Then think about it slowly
Please wait until you think about it before contacting me.
I'm going to be late. All subsequent appointments will be postponed.
ok ok
So do you want to buy it?
Good
come sit down
In that case...
What?
Please discuss it with your wife before you come back.
Oops, why are you making things so difficult for me?
This way we can all feel at ease
I use my own money
Why discuss with others?
Come back soon
- OK
- Really
In that case, boss
Please pay the deposit now.
We need to lock down the property quickly
Otherwise, the next wave of customers will have to travel in vain.
- How much?
- 10% of the total price
Wait, I have something to ask you. It's very important.
Don't tell other owners
You took a discount of 550 million
Otherwise we'll be in big trouble
I can't. Don't worry.
This is a special discount just for you
Other owners bought it at the original price.
Do you understand?
thank you
(Sign up: Pediatrics, Dentistry
pharmacies, restaurants, dermatology)
Welcome I'm waiting for you
Many customers are waiting
If you sign the contract now...
Metro station...
1.2 billion won is really the lowest price
This place is a great deal
This price really can't be any lower
I don't have to go to the company to work anymore
Nak Soo who earns tens of millions per month
Nak Soo who earns tens of millions per month!
Where have you been? I don’t answer the phone either.
What is this? Can't you eat something good?
I wanted to go out to eat with you
But you don't answer the phone
Where did Soo Gyeom go?
Soo Gyeom? He’s out
- Wife
- Huh?
What are you doing? Hello!
What's the matter with you? Husband!
old...
Stop! Don't do this!
(Mocha bean coffee)
- Welcome
- Ouch
Welcome boss
Is business pretty good?
yes
The store is so big
Dad, does this place really belong to you?
Could you please bring three cups of coffee to that table?
OK I will do it for you myself
- OK
- Yeah
Please sit down
This place is really nice
- Minister Do, the problem lies with you.
- sorry
wow
Good guy!
- Ouch
- Look who this is
- Senior
- Oops
- Hello
- My light, my joy
- Oops
- My Zhuge Kongming
Oops
Congratulations on your grand opening.
(Congratulations on the opening)
Put it over there
- Hello
- not there
Then put it on the ground
- you boy
- OK
No eyesight at all
How's it going at the company?
Without Secretary Kim, nothing can be done.
Can't you go back to the company?
I promise to give you special treatment
I'm just tired of being a wage earner.
Isn't that right, Minister Dou?
I didn't understand your ambition before
Many words and deeds are offensive
- Sorry
- Hello!
Stop talking nonsense
Go buy us coffee
- With my own money?
- No need
Just put it in my account
Just order whatever you want to drink
thank you
Really
I'm really sorry about what happened last time
It's okay. You said that out of kindness.
On the contrary, I should apologize, Mr. Bai
sorry
Why are you doing this? Please
Just like before, call me brother
Bark
Husband, call me one
Brother
you are happy
Brother-in-law!
Hello everyone
- Who is this?
- Oh hey
This is the life of a real man
I admire you so much
Sister, I was presumptuous last time
I have been reflecting on my behavior
I'm so sorry
It's okay, just leave it there
Minister Kim!
Hey!
- Hello everyone
- Hello Minister
We all heard the good news
I have really studied real estate for so long in vain.
Our company's employees
Minister, you are indeed the best.
Have you all eaten?
- Not yet
- Oops
Take this and eat whatever you want.
After eating, come back here for coffee
Really? Then we can order Dudari's
- Special package?
- Hey!
Go to the Japanese BBQ restaurant across the street
Order the best beef and eat all you want without a menu
thank you so much
- thank you
- Congratulations on the opening
- We went first. Come find us.
- OK
- I'll go too
- Chengjiu Hi
What the hell?
What...
- What are you doing? Come on!
- OK
coffee is here
Good
Divide it
- Sorry
- Let's divide it
- give
- Put it all away
give
Senior
I have some prostate problems recently
Can I have a tomato sandwich?
OK, eat it
Got this disease at such a young age
It must be too much pressure
That thing of yours must be bad, right?
Oops you are right
It’s not wine, but let’s have a drink, too?
Then...
OK Cheers
- Congratulations to Minister Kim!
- Congratulations!
Cheers
"Cheers"? Oops
Wife?
- Just go back to sleep
- Wife
Compared with receiving retirement benefits in one lump sum
Choose the form of pension payment
- You can pay less tax
- Please help me terminate the contract
Good
I also want to apply for a personal loan
Personal loan?
Please fill out this form
Good
(Opening soon)
- Really?
- Really
- Your choice is too wise
- I knew it
Yes I understand
If any customer gives up their quota, I will tell you immediately
You have reached your destination
Let’s take a look!
(Time spent: 3 minutes and 56 seconds)
Even if you walk slowly
It only takes three minutes from the subway station.
Great!
You'll be opening soon too!
Let me see what it is?
(Director of Store Sales Office)
“The balance has been received, thank you!”
Ah? Hello
Recently?
I'm managing a small building
Monthly rent? About 10 million won per month
It’s just pocket money, right?
(Yansi University)
(shareholding status)
(Hanjiang Retail LAV Biologics
ASK-VAN GROUP)
(Hankwang Semiconductor Blue Future Energy)
I'm very happy during this time. Goodbye.
(sell everything)
See you next time
(Sell order confirmed)
(Sell order has been submitted successfully)
(Bank deposit notification)
(Income from Kim Nak-soo: 30 million won)
"Thirty million"?
Get ready!
dad
Dad, this money...
Did you lie to me?
You kid, how dare you lie to your father?
Do you think that is filial piety?
sorry
Do you think I'm so incompetent?
Thirty million is nothing. My son was cheated.
Even if it is three billion
Dad can still help you pay it back, do you understand?
What a man, why are you so worried about this little money?
If you were like this now
How can I become a great person in the future?
thank you dad
Are you okay now?
It's okay
Okay, take it as a lesson.
So what is destruction and jealousy?
That company representative should resign immediately.
Go to school well, okay?
If you don’t want to study anymore, then join the army early.
After joining the army, study hard
Get into a better university
ok?
Anyway, if anything happens, call me right away.
- OK
-Put your chest out!
(Hannah)
(utterly bored
Thoughts...distractions...it's time to say goodbye)
Hello?
Hey boss, how are you doing lately?
There is a store that wants to sign a contract, so I would like to contact you specifically.
Ah, what kind of store is it?
It's a toast shop
Toast...toast shop?
Boss, actually this is more suitable than a coffee shop.
Now that the economy is in recession, everyone pays attention to benefits
But the store is so big
Toast? Isn’t that something only children eat?
No, office workers now eat toast as their main meal.
There are also whole wheat and vegetarian versions
But this is so different from what you said originally
Then I can help you find a coffee shop
If you are not in a hurry to gain
Dad, let me go out for a while
Wait Hey Soo Gyom
- Huh?
- When was the last time you had toast?
- What?
- Toast. The kind you eat.
Toast? I don’t know.
Dad, I'm in a hurry
Wait
Hey Soo Kyum
You just came back...
If you need anything, call me
Sorry, Dad, I'll be right back
He just came back. Where is he going? Hello?
No matter what you think
I still think cafes are better...
Boss, now only your shop is empty.
If it stays empty, I don’t know what others will think.
Boss, it’s a toast shop
But it’s actually a large chain brand
They said the monthly rent can be 9 million
What about the security deposit?
Twenty million
Isn’t a 20 million deposit too small?
Quite a few, boss
What is popular now is
The monthly rent is higher and the security deposit is lower.
What do you think?
It doesn't matter to me. It's all up to you.
Okay, let’s sign the contract
Then I'll pay the deposit now.
Then prepare the contract
Good bye
Good
Not bad Not bad
Not bad Quite good
(taxi)
- Master, are you going to Incheon Airport?
- Right
- Could you please hurry up?
- OK
Hello?
Sorry, Hana, don't go to the United States.
What?
Please don't go
I got my dad's investment
I have put down all my thoughts and distractions...
And that kiss
I erased it all. I've made up my mind.
it's you
thank you
(The power of jealousy)
Be careful on the road
You already have a part-time job
What's the emergency? Why did you take a taxi here?
What’s up with the airport photos?
I sent it in advance
I haven’t booked my flight tickets yet.
So? You don’t want me to go to America?
I'm leaving
Don't go
sorry
me too
money from selling things
How about taking it for a beer?
Let's go
The two bosses only need here and here
And just sign your name here, okay
(Deposit: 20 million won
Monthly rent: 9 million won)
Our headquarters also said that this location is very good.
Right
Thank you so much. We will do a good job.
You're welcome. I'm glad to rent it to you.
- thank you
OK, please exchange contracts.
- Just like before...
- OK
- ...just sign again
(Lessor: Kim Nak-soo)
(Contracted: Pediatrics, Dentistry
pharmacies, restaurants, dermatology)
(Huiyin Psychiatric Clinic)
(Wangzhen Shopping Center Sales Office
Steady income, reliable investment)
Have you ever made eye contact with a seagull?
No
Have you ever sprained your feet trying to avoid a seagull?
Sorry, hello.
Hello, how can I help you?
Wangzhen Shopping Center over there
I am the owner of a corner store on the ground floor
Wangzhen Shopping Center? Oh, what’s wrong?
I heard that several clinics are sure to move in.
Do you know when it will move in?
I'm not sure about this
- Did you know?
- Don't know
Right
There is a clinic on the second floor that has started accepting patients.
Really?
Which one is it from?
Please leave your contact information
Let me help you see if anyone wants to rent your shop
No need, I've already rented it out
- OK
- You guys are busy first. Goodbye.
- How did he rent it out?
- Does this make sense?
(Zhongying Real Estate)
(Physical examination results Kim Nak-soo)
(Blood test hemoglobin 15.2)
Hemoglobin 15.2
Is it on the high side or on the low side?
How do I know?
好的 我来解释一下吧
you are very healthy
Oops thanks
I just said I'm fine
Cardiopulmonary function, bone density
Blood pressure indicators are very good
Especially cardiopulmonary function
You're pretty good at your age.
I've been doing anaerobic sprints lately
When?
In the factory, I didn't tell you
Liver indicators are normal and cholesterol is also normal.
Wow, the results are so good. It’s time to drink some wine.
Did you hear that?
In addition, your reproductive function is also very healthy
Sperm count, motility, morphology...
All are excellent
How about I run for the "Endurance King"?
Stop making trouble
But your stress level is a bit high
You must be very busy at work, right?
I recently resigned
That should get better soon
Just keep exercising
What is my biological age?
Biological age?
41 years old
41! I am the endurance king!
Really what?
The doctor said my biological age is 41 years old
In other words, you are living with a younger man.
Got it
Luo Su, while you are still healthy, find a job.
- Listen to your sister.
- Good sister
Ouch, I really can’t stand you
What's going on with that smile of yours?
Ha Jin, let’s go out for dinner.
(lazy guy)
Why are you going out to eat? Stop wasting money
No. I have something to tell you.
On a day like this, you have to go to a good place
leave lasting memories
Have you found a job?
I'll tell you later
Hey, it’s this guy again
(missed call lazy guy)
Why does he keep calling?
That's good news, right?
I'll tell you later
I'm leaving. See you later.
(Bangui Real Estate Agency)
Hello
- Please come in
- Hello
good morning
- good morning
- Hi
(information)
(lazy guy)
(...scams targeting retirees)
I've been thinking about it for several days, but I still have to tell you.
Don't think about unreliable things, please, my friend.
Call the store sales manager
(Director of Store Sales Office)
The number you dialed is unavailable
Please check before calling...
Call the store sales manager
The number you dialed is unavailable
Please check before dialing
The one you dialed...
Call the toast shop owner
(Call the toast shop owner)
(Toast shop owner)
Hello?
Hello, I am the landlord
When are you going to start decorating?
Ah...
What should I do? I might not be able to open that store.
What? What are you talking about?
We have signed the contract
I'm very sorry that the store can't open.
You can't quit suddenly now...
What about the security deposit?
Oh, you don’t need to return the deposit.
- Goodbye
- Hello?
Call the toast shop owner
The number you dialed is temporarily unavailable
Please leave a message after the beep
(lazy guy)
(...scams targeting retirees)
(Revealing policies targeting retirees
income-based real estate fraud)
(Pressure tactic: pretending to be scarce)
How long until the next appointment?
About 15 minutes?
Boss, I'm afraid I only have about 15 minutes
Do you think it will work?
Okay, let me give you a brief introduction.
- Head of the room
- Ah, is it time?
Are you on your way?
No. I will be available to see you after my next appointment.
The monthly salary will be cut off...
- No monthly rent!
The headquarters of a large IT company is to be built nearby
Project has been approved
Almost all the 50,000 residents in the surrounding communities have moved in.
(fictitious location and requirements)
Including VAT, it’s almost 9.9 million
(overstated earnings)
You can just rent it for 10 million a month.
There are no resale restrictions here.
Turn around and add an extra 400 million to sell on the market
Will take action immediately
You can make 400 million just by sitting down
Don't tell other owners
You took a discount of 550 million
Otherwise we'll be in big trouble
This is a special discount just for you
Other owners bought it at the original price.
Oops, you're here again
Did something happen to the store opposite?
Shop?
Oh, Wangzhen Shopping Center
The TV station came to film it last week
Everyone must have seen the content of the program
I heard that the store could not be sold for even 300 million won.
They sold more than a billion
- It's too much
- Oops
Wait, you didn’t spend one billion to buy the store, right?
It's a three-minute walk from here
Prime location just to the subway station
- How could it be worth only 300 million?
- Ouch, what did you say?
The subway project has been delayed for a long time
How can it be considered a subway business district if it is not open to traffic?
It seems like he really doesn't know.
I didn't expect you to actually sign the contract
Are the utility bills also borne by you?
Yeah
(Sales and Rent Wangzhen Shopping Center Sales Office)
According to investigation
The sales office issued an unauthorized development plan
Inducing customers to sign contracts quickly
and used a fake list of merchants as bait.
Lure investors into taking the bait
Help open the door!
Hurry up!
(Wangzhen Shopping Center)
(urgent sale)
(Urgent sale, one-year short-term rental, super urgent sale)
(urgent sale office or shop)
"Minister Kim's Dream Life"
Didn’t I tell you not to touch your severance pay?
Don’t think about carrying it alone
Tell your wife quickly
Are you hiding something from me?
You've been doing weird things lately
It feels like I’m interviewing you, brother-in-law.
If that’s the case
Then I’ll start working today, okay?
Soo Qian, when will you do this?
That circle didn’t protect you.
If you are overwhelmed by debt
Do you know what the consequences will be?
Eventually you will lose yourself
Damn it
Who are you?
Are you...
Fate is such a wonderful thing, isn’t it?
I didn’t expect that we would work together again.
Subtitle translation: Cheng Jiayue